let currentPage = 0
let quiz = [
    {
        "question": "According to Google, what year was JavaScript invented?",
        "options": ["2023", "1995", "1985", "2003"],
        "answer": "1995"
    },
    {
        "question": "What's 2+2?",
        "options": ["I don't know math", "undefined", "3", "4"],
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following fruits are typically red?",
        "options": ["Apple", "Orange", "Banana", "Watermelon"],
        "answer": "Apple"
    },
    {
        "question": "How long does it take for me to drive to school everyday?",
        "options": ["12 years", "30 minutes", "15 minutes", "3 seconds"],
        "answer": "30 minutes"
    },
    {
        "question": "How much wood could a woodchuck chuck...",
        "options": ["...What?", "...if a woodchuck could chuck wood?", "...700 pounds of wood, actually.", "...Who?"],
        "answer": "...if a woodchuck could chuck wood?"
    },
    {
        "question": "What question number are you on now?",
        "options": ["3", "5", "6", "5.591"],
        "answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is my favorite number?",
        "options": ["22", "33", "7", "8"],
        "answer": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is my favorite word?",
        "options": ["Boolean", "Sassafras", "Interesting", "Exit"],
        "answer": "Exit"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is my favorite color?",
        "options": ["Hot pink", "A deep purple", "Literally just blue", "Bright neon green"],
        "answer": "Hot pink"
    },
    {
        "question": "How long did it take for me to think of questions for this?",
        "options": ["These are questions?", "Who knows", "20 minutes", "All day"],
        "answer": "20 minutes"
    }
]

function submit(){
}